{
    "subject": "resource/Clarissa_S._Williams",
    "predicate": "property/deathCause",
    "object": "resource/Nephritis",
    "human_readable": "The death cause of Clarissa S. Williams was Nephritis.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9405544996261597,
            "question": "What was the cause of Clarissa S. Williams' death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8191794157028198,
            "question": "Did Clarissa S. Williams die from a medical condition?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8102257251739502,
            "question": "What medical term describes Clarissa S. Williams' cause of death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8096007108688354,
            "question": "Were there any other contributing factors to Clarissa S. Williams' death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7807608246803284,
            "question": "Is Nephritis a common cause of death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30087289214134216,
            "question": "What are the symptoms of Nephritis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2527258098125458,
            "question": "Nephritis is a disease affecting what organ?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23010927438735962,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about Nephritis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21090981364250183,
            "question": "How is Nephritis treated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15314505994319916,
            "question": "Are there any preventative measures for Nephritis?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The death cause of Clarissa S. Williams was Nephritis.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2269_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is Nephritis treated?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2269_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide more information about Nephritis?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2269_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nephritis is a disease affecting what organ?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2269_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2269_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2269_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2269_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2269_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2269_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2269_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2269_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2269_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2269_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2269_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like me to analyze more triples!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that none of the documents mention Clarissa Williams' death being caused by nephritis, and one document even states that her death appears to have been the result of drowning."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not mention any information related to the cause of death for Clarissa S. Williams being nephritis. The document only mentions that her death appeared to be the result of drowning, pending further autopsy results."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The context information does not provide any evidence to suggest that Clarissa S. Williams died due to nephritis. Her death was caused by drowning, as stated in the text, and an official cause of death has not been determined yet, pending autopsy results and toxicology testing.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text states that Clarissa Williams died after driving her car into a pond, and her death appears to have been the result of drowning.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "It was explicitly stated in the context information (point 3) that \"Williams' death appears to have been the result of drowning, but the coroner's autopsy report that would include the results of toxicology testing and official cause of death has not been completed.\" This implies that the actual cause of death is still unknown or undetermined.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information provided states that Clarissa Williams' death appears to have been the result of drowning, not nephritis.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}